reasonablespread.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy | Reasonable Spread

At Reasonable Software, we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our websites. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to all Reasonable Software websites, products and services.

## Information Collection and Use 

Reasonable Software is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Reasonable Software collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Our websites offers several opportunities for visitors to register for promotional and informational mailings, online webinars and resources, and for assistance in evaluating our software and services. These registration forms are often linked to Reasonable Spread's mailing lists and require users to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this contact information to send users information about our company and its products and services if requested or necessary. Users may unsubscribe future mailings at any time (see the choice/opt-out section below).

## Sharing and Use

We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. Occasionally, we enter into contracts with third parties so that they can assist us in servicing you (for example, providing customer service). We may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request.

## Use of Web Technologies

We use a variety of technologies on our sites. Among these are cookies; a piece of information that our websites provide to your browser when you visit our sites. Cookies allow us to verify the login status of customers using products or services linked directly with our website, track point of entry to point of registration for those users participating in our affiliate signup programs, and to track and measure the success of a particular marketing campaign. Cookies also allow us to track overall site usage and determine areas users prefer, enabling us to make your visit to our websites easier by recognizing you when you return and helping to provide you with a customized experience. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If you choose to disable cookies, you may still use our site; however, you may have limited access to some areas within our websites.

When we send you emails, we may include a single-pixel GIF to allow us to determine the number of people who open our emails. When you click on a link in an email, we record this individual response to allow us to customize our offerings to you.

We also keep track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. Once you leave our site, we do not track you. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites and to tailor our product and service offerings to you.

## External Links

Some of our sites provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. While on these sites, Reasonable Software or its partners may collect information about you. Because Reasonable Software does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

## Personal Data Security 

We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information by using industry-recognized security safeguards such as firewalls, coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of encryption during transmission, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Reasonable Software takes care to reinforce the importance of our website visitors' security and privacy among our employees. Our employees are trained and required to safeguard your information and, using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards, we restrict access to personal information to those employees and agents for business purposes only. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

## Choice

Reasonable Software provides users the opportunity to subscribe, unsubscribe or change preferences via a link in the footer of most email messages. These options are made available when you sign-up for our email lists and in email messages delivered from our company. Alternatively, you may email us at spread[at]reasonables.com.

We reserve the right to send important account notifications and billing information necessary to all Reasonable Software users and customers. You must cancel your Reasonable Software account to unsubscribe from these communications. To cancel your Reasonable Spread account, please email us at spread[at]reasonables.com.

## Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the Reasonable Software Website. So our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
